Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the Vice-President Records 1937-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Shubart, Harry, November-January, 1940-1941 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Shubart, Harry, February-April, 1940-1941 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Shubart, Harry, May-June, 1940-1941 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Shubart, Harry, July-October, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Shubart, Harry, November-June, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Shubart, Harry, "War and the University," Woodlawn League of Women Voters, 20 April 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Simons, Henry, 1937-1938 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Sixth Corps Area, orientation course, lecturers expense account sheets, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Sixth Corps Area, Chanute Field, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Sixth Corps Area, Camp Grant, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Sixth Corps Area, Camp McCoy, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Sixth Corps Area, camps, miscellaneous, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Sixth Corps Area, Camp Savanna, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Sixth Corps Area, Camp Scott, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Sixth Corps Area, Camp Sheridan, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Sixth Corps Area, speakers, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Sixth Corps Area, speaker suggestions, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Sixth Corps Area, University, 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Sixth Corps Area, Washington, D. C., Major Lincoln, 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Sixth Corps Area, Washington, D. C., Chicago headquarters, 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Sixth Corps Area, Washington, D. C., Captain Rosengren, 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Sloan, Alfred P., 1939-1940 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Sloan, Alfred P., 1940-1941 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Sloan, Alfred P., 1943-1944 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Sloan, Alfred P., 1944-1945 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Smith, T. V., 1940-1941 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Smith, T. V., 1942-1943 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Souvaine, Henry, 1940-1941 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Speakers' Bureau, 1938-1939 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Speakers' Bureau, lists, 1938-1939 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Speakers' Bureau, 1939-1940 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Speakers' Bureau, July-December, 1940-1941 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Speakers' Bureau, January-June, 1940-1941 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Speakers' Bureau, 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Speakers' Bureau, 1942-1943 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- Speakers' Bureau, 1943-1944 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Speakers' Bureau, 1944-1945 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Spencer, Dean William H., 1937-1938 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Spencer, Dean William H., 1938-1939 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- Spencer, Dean William H., 1942-1943 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- Spencer, Lyle M., 1939-1940 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- St. John's College, 1938-1939 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Steere, Lloyd, 1939-1940 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Steere, Lloyd, 1940-1941 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Steere, Lloyd, 1941-1942 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Steere, Lloyd, 1942-1943 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Steere, Lloyd, 1943-1944 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Stewart, Dr. Irwin, 1937-1938 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Stifler, James, 1937-1938 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Stifler, James, 1938-1939 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Stifler, James, 1939-1940 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Struve, Otto, 1940-1941 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Student selection, 1937-1938 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Stutzman, Frances, 1939-1940 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Stutzman, Frances, 1942-1943 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Stutzman, Frances, 1943-1944 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Stutzman, Frances, 1944-1945 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Stutzman, Frances, 1945-1946 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Swift, Harold, 1937-1938 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Swift, Harold, 1938-1939 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Swift, Harold H., 1939-1940 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Swift, Harold H., 1940-1941 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Swift, Harold H., "The University and the Trustee," 1940-1941 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Swift, Harold H., 1941-1942 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Swift, Harold H., 1942-1943 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Swift, Harold H., 1943-1944 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Swift, Harold H., 1944-1945 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- T, general, 1937-1938, Thomason, S. E. Temple Topics Three Acres Security Town Hall of the Air Tracey, E. A. Treadwell, George L. (Box 55, Folder 10)
- T, general, 1938-1939, Thresher, Mrs. B. Alden Time Toigo, Avinere Towner, Ethelyn Town Meeting of the Air (Box 55, Folder 11)
- T, general, 1939-1940, Taliaferro, W. H. Talley, Howard Teter, Lucius Thomason, S. E. Thompson, Helen Reid Thorp, Willard Tide Time Toigo, Avinere Torell, Frank Tower, W. S. Tower Topics View of the Quadrangles Town Hall Townsend, Harold Tyler, Ralph (Box 55, Folder 12)
- T, general, 1940-1941, Tamblyn-Brown Tan, S. H. Tenenbaum, Dr. Joseph Thomas, J. Elmer Thompson, Dorothy Thompson, Frederick I. Thompson, J. Walter Co. Thompson, John Thompson, Warren E. Tillery, Dale Time Todd, Jessie Tregillus, C. A. Turovin, Leonard Tyler, I. Keith (Box 55, Folder 13)
- T, general, 1941-1942, Taliaferro, W. H. Tallman, Bertha Taylor, Thomas R. Taylor, Wayne C. Tefft, Sheldon Thompson, Dorothy Thomson, Ruth Thurstone, L. L. Time Timothy, P. H. Toigo, Avinere Tomlinson, William Topping, Harry Tovrov, Orin Town Meeting Tracht, Fred H. Truman, H. F. Tucker, Austin E. Tulane University Tunis, John Turabian, Kate Turner, C. A. Tyler, I. Keith Tyler, R. W. (Box 55, Folder 14)
- T, general, 1942-1943, Taft, Robert A. Taliaferro, W. H. Tead, Ordway Thompson, Dan Trevino, Salomon Trippe, Juan Turabian, Kate Twentieth Century Fund (Box 55, Folder 15)
- T, general, 1943-1944, Tefft, Sheldon Thomas, Norman Thompson, Charles Thompson, Marion Thornberry, C. O. Thornberry, John Thornton, Iona Thrasher, Corrinne Thurston, Lorrin Times, London Town Meeting Trippe, Juan Trumbull, William R. J. Turabian, Kate L. Tyler, I. Keith Tyler, Tracy (Box 55, Folder 16)
- T, general, 1944-1945, Taylor, Howard C. Tefft, Sheldon Teng, S. Y. Terborgh, George Thompson, Clem Thompson, H. A. Thurstone, L. L. Timperley, H. J. Truman, Harry (Box 55, Folder 17)
- T, general, 1945-1946, Tefft, Sheldon Thurstone, L. L. Tokunaga, Mabel Tyler, I. Keith (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Taliaferro, William H., 1940-1941 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Tamblyn & Brown, 1937-1938 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Taylor, Dr. Howard C., Jr., 1938-1939 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Taylor, Dr. Howard C., Jr., 1939-1940 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Taylor, Dr. Howard C., Jr., Committee on Maternal Health, 1942-1943 (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Tax exemptions, 1939-1940 (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Tax memorandum, 1942-1943 (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Telephone Survey, 1939-1940 (Box 55, Folder 26)
- Telephone Survey, 1940-1941 (Box 55, Folder 27)
- Texas, 1940-1941 (Box 55, Folder 28)
- Texas, 1941-1942 (Box 55, Folder 29)
- This Week, 1937-1938 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- This Week, 1938-1939 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- This Week, 1939-1940 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- This Week, 1940-1941 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- This Week, 1942-1943 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- This Week, 1943-1944 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- This Week, 1945-1946 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Thomason, S. E., 1940-1941 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Thomason, S. E., 1941-1942 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Thomason, S. E., 1942-1943 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Thomason, S. E., 1943-1944 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Thompson, Dorothy, 1937-1938 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Thomson, Ruth, 1942-1943 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Thurstone, Louis L., 1940-1941 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Thurstone, Louis L, work of, 1940-1941 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Time, Eric Hodgins, 1941-1942 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Time, Henry R. Luce, 1941-1942 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Time-Life memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- Time, general, 1942-1943 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- Time, Eric Hodgins, 1942-1943 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Time, Henry R. Luce, 1942-1943 (Box 56, Folder 21)
- Time, 1943-1944 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Time, general, 1944-1945 (Box 56, Folder 23)
- Time, fellowships, 1945-1946 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Time, general, 1945-1946 (Box 56, Folder 25)
- Tuition plan, 1942-1943 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Tunis, John R., 1937-1938 (Box 56, Folder 27)
- Tunis, John R., including "What Price Football", 1939-1940 (Box 56, Folder 28)
- Tunis, John R., 1940-1941 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Tunis, John R., 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Tunis, John R., 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Tunis, John R., 1944-1945 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Tunis, John R., 1945-1946 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Tyler, Ralph, 1940-1941 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Tyler, Ralph, 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Tyler, Ralph, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Tyler, Ralph, 1944-1945 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- U, general, 1938-1939, U. S. Superintendent of Documents (Box 57, Folder 10)
- U, general, 1939-1940, Utley, Clifton (Box 57, Folder 11)
- U, general, 1940-1941, United States Post Office Universal Distributors Unzicker, Frances V. Utley, Clifton (Box 57, Folder 12)
- U, general, 1941-1942, Uncensored United Air Lines U. S. Marine Corps United States Post Office University Club University Laboratory Schools Unlimited Horizons Utley, Clifton (Box 57, Folder 13)
- U, general, 1942-1943, United Air Lines United States Navy University Club (Box 57, Folder 14)
- U, general, 1943-1944, United Air Lines Upham, Charles U. S. Civil Service Commission U. S. Maritime Commission (Box 57, Folder 15)
- United China Relief, 1941-1942 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- University Films Society, 1937-1938 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- "University of Chicago," E. E. Slosson, The Independent, 1910, 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- University of Chicago Clinics, 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 19)
- University of Chicago, Life, 16 July 1945, 1945-1946 (Box 57, Folder 20)
- University War Activities, 1945-1946 (Box 57, Folder 21)
- V, general, 1937-1938, Vahlteich, H. W. – Carlson, A. J. Visuphonic Pictures Viner, Jacob Von Boershelman, Natasha, Fortune article on radio broadcasting and manufacturing Von Schever, Walter (Box 57, Folder 22)
- V, general, 1938-1939, Vanderbilt University VerNooy, Winifred Viner, Jacob Visher, Stephen S. (Box 57, Folder 22)
- V, general, 1939-1940, Van Wesep, H. B. VerNooy, Winifred Viner, Jacob Viol, Mary Visher, S. S. Visser, Edwin (Box 57, Folder 23)
- V, general, 1940-1941, Van de Water, John Van Kirk, James A. Viner, Jacob Visher, S. S. Vocational Guidance and Placement (Box 57, Folder 24)
- V, general, 1941-1942, Vale, J. D. Valentine, Alan Vandenberg, A. S. Van der Meer, Abram Van Nice, Errett Vaughan, L. Brent Volwiler, Dr. Ernest (Box 57, Folder 25)
- V, general, 1942-1943, Villard, O. G. Viner, Jacob (Box 57, Folder 26)
- V, general, 1943-1944, Valentine, John Van Doren, Mark Vermilya, H. P. Vollasenor, Eduardo Viner, Jacob Vinson, L. E. (Box 57, Folder 27)
- V, general, 1944-1945, Vanderpoel, Robert Vansittart, Lord Van Vlissingen, Arthur Velie, Lester Vickrey, C. V. Viner, Jacob Vinson, Fred (Box 57, Folder 28)
- V, general, 1945-1946, Viner, Jacob (Box 57, Folder 29)
- Vice-President special budget, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 30)
- Vice-President special budget, 1944-1945 (Box 57, Folder 31)
- W, general, 1937-1938, Waite, E. A. Waldeck, Herman Wallace, DeWitt Webbe, William Wei, Francis Wollard, James Wells, H. Gideon Western Union White, B. H. Whiting, Lawrence (Box 57, Folder 32)
- W, general, 1937-1938, Wickhem, Valerie Wild, Arthur Williams, Robert R. Wilson, John P. Wilson, Louis R. Wirth, Louis Woellner, Robert Wright, Frank Writers' Press Association (Box 57, Folder 33)
- W, general, 1938-1939, Warner, Charles Wasson, R. Gordon Watkins, Myron H. Watson, J. Donald WBBM WCFL Welles, Orson West, Royce Whitaker, John T. White, Leonard D. Woods, L. A. (Box 57, Folder 34)
- W, general, 1938-1939, Wickhem, Valerie Wild, Arthur Willey, Malcolm M. Williamson, Mrs. Walter G. Wilson, Charles Wilson, John Woman's Day Women's City Club Wright, Joseph P. Wright, Quincy (Box 57, Folder 35)
- W, general, 1939-1940, Walker, Paul Walker, Sydney Wall Street Journal Waples, Douglas Warner, Julia Washington Alumni Club Watson, B. Frank Weber, Pearl Weinberg, Louis Werntz, George West, Royce Western Reserve University White, T. J. White, Tom Murray (Box 57, Folder 36)
- W, general, 1939-1940, Wickhem, Valerie Wieboldt Foundation Wild, Arthur Wilk, Jacob, Warner Brothers Windsor, Henry Wirth, Louis Woman's Day Woodloch, Thomas F. Wright, Joseph F. Wright, Mrs. Quincy Wright, Quincy Wright, Warren (Box 57, Folder 37)
- W, general, 1940-1941, Walker, Gladys Walker, Paul Walker, Walter Walsh, Earle J. Warner, W. Lloyd Waters, Lewis Watson, B. Frank Watson Weeks, I. D. Weiss, Louis Welles, Donald Welles, Edward Welles, Orson Welsh, Earl Westwater, Davis WGN Wheeler, Burton K. Wheeler, Laura Whitacre, H. Whitcomb, H. J. White, Leonard D. White, Tom Murray Whitney, Cornelius V. Whittlesey, E. D. (Box 57, Folder 38)
- W, general, 1940-1941, Wide World Photos, Inc. Wilbur, Ray Lyman Wild, Arthur Wilder, Thornton Wilk, Jacob Wilkerson, W. M. Wilkinson, Robert Williamson, Mrs. Walter Willits, Joseph H. Willkie, Wendell Wilson, John P. Wilson, Louis R. Wilson, William J. Wood, Robert Wright, Thomas Wright, Warren Wrigley, Philip K. (Box 57, Folder 39)
- W, general, 1941-1942, Wagner, Paul Walker, Paul Wallace, Henry A. Walling, A. K. Walsh, Elmer Wanger, Walter War Department Warner, W. Lloyd Watson, Nancy Waymack, W. W. Weber, Theodore Weinberg, Sidney Weinberger, Howard Weise, Louise Welles, Orson Wepman, Joseph Western Electric Whaley, Verne Wheeler, Burton K. White, Leonard D. White, Tom Murray Whitmarsh, Agnes Whitney, A. F. (Box 57, Folder 40)
- W, general, 1941-1942, Wickhem, Valerie Wiese, J. B. Wilbur, Raymond Wild, Arthur Wilder, Thornton Wilkinson, R. Wilson, Charles Wilson, Charles E. Wilson, John A. Wilson, Logan Wilson, Louis R. Wilson, M. L. Wilson, Richard Windsor, Henry Wittacker, Jack World-Wide Broadcasting System Wright, George C. Wrigley, Philip K. Wylie, Max (Box 57, Folder 41)
- W, general, 1942-1943, Waite, E. A. Walgreen Lectures Walker, Charles Wallace, H. A. Wanger, Walter War Department Wherry, Larry (Box 57, Folder 42)
- W, general, 1942-1943, Wilder, Russell Wilgus, A. Curtis Wilk, Jacob Wilkinson, Albert E. Wilkinson, Robert A. Willkie, Wendell Wilt, Napier Wirth, Louis Woellner, Robert Wright, Mrs. Quincy Writers' Conference (Box 57, Folder 43)
- W, general, 1943-1944, Wallace, E. H. Warner, Lloyd Wasson, Gordon Webster, B. Western Union White, Compton White, Leonard White, T. J. White, Tom Whitley, Sarah (Box 58, Folder 1)
- W, general, 1943-1944, Wikgren, Allen P. Wilk, Benjamin Wilkoff, Ralph M. Willey, M. W. Williams, H. D. Wiltberger, Constance Wilson, O. F. Wilson, R. R. Wolseley, M. E. Woodson, Carter G. Wright, Chester Wright, Louise Wynner, Edith (Box 58, Folder 2)
- W, general, 1944-1945, Walker, E. Jerry Wallace, Everett H. Wallace, Henry Waring, Frank Warren, Ahrens Publishing Co. Wayeright, Victor Waymack, W. W. Weinberg, Sidney J. Weitzer, Bernard Welles, Orson Wertheim, Maurice Wheeler, Burton K. Wheeler, Jack White, Arthur D. White, Compton I. White, Leonard D. Whittlesey, C. R. Whittemore, Jean Who's Who (Box 58, Folder 3)
- W, general, 1944-1945, Willits, Joseph H. Wilson, John A. Wilt, Napier Winter, E. W. Wolfe, Albert P. Wood, James M. Wood, R. Warner Wood, Robert E. Woodward, Mrs. Frederic Wright, Quincy (Box 58, Folder 4)
- W, general, 1945-1946, Wikgren, Allen P. Wilson, John Wilt, Napier Woellner, Robert Wolters, Larry Wood, James Wright, Quincy (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Walgreen Chair, 1937-1938 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Walgreen Chair, 1938-1939 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Walgreen Chair, 1939-1940 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Walgreen Investigation, 1935, statement of Robert M. Hutchins, "Service of the University to the Community", 1939-1940 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Walker, Commissioner Paul A., 1937-1938 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Wallace, Henry A., 1943-1944 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Wanger, Walter, 1940-1941 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Waples, Douglas, 1940-1941 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Waples, Douglas, 1941-1942 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Waples, Douglas, 1942-1943 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- Weidenrich, Franz, 1937-1938 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Weidenrich, Franz, 1938-1939 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- White, T. J., 1940-1941 (Box 58, Folder 18)
- White, T. J., 1942-1943 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- White, T. J., 1943-1944 (Box 58, Folder 20)
- White, T. J., 1944-1945 (Box 58, Folder 21)
- Whiting, Frank S., 1937-1938 (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Wiese, Otis L., 1939-1940 (Box 58, Folder 23)
- Williamsburg, John D. Rockefeller III, 1940-1941 (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Windsor, Henry, 1940-1941 (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Winter, Edwin W., 1937-1938 (Box 58, Folder 26)
- Winter, Edwin W., 1938-1939 (Box 58, Folder 27)
- Winter, Edwin W., 1941-1942 (Box 58, Folder 28)
- Winter, Edwin W., 1942-1943 (Box 58, Folder 29)
- Winter, Edwin W., 1943-1944 (Box 58, Folder 30)
- Wirth, Louis, 1940-1941 (Box 58, Folder 31)
- Wirth, Louis, 1941-1942 (Box 58, Folder 32)
- Wirth, Louis, 1943-1944 (Box 58, Folder 33)
- Woellner, Robert C., 1941-1942 (Box 58, Folder 34)
- Woellner, Robert C., 1943-1944 (Box 58, Folder 35)
- Women's Events, 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Women's Events, correspondence with H. B. Harvey, 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Women's Luncheon invitation list, 1937-1938 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Wood, General Robert E., 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Wood, General Robert E., 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Woodward, Frederic, 1937-1938 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Woodward, Frederic, 1938-1939 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Woodward, Frederic, 1939-1940 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Woodward, Frederic, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Woodward, Frederic, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Woodward, Frederic, 1943-1944 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Words of American Origin, 1937-1938 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Works, George A., 1937-1938 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Works, George A., 1939-1940 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Works, George A., 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- Wright, Quincy, 1937-1938 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- Wright, Quincy, 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Wright, Quincy, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Wright, Quincy, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 19)
- Wright, Quincy, 1943-1944 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Y, general, 1937-1938 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Y, general, 1938-1939, Young, Gurney K. (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Y, general, 1939-1940, Yen, Y. C. Yntema, Theodore O. (Box 59, Folder 23)
- Y, general, 1940-1941, Yen, Y. C. Young, Stanley Preston (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Y, general, 1941-1942, Yale University Yntema, Theodore O. Young, James R. Young, James W. (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Y, general, 1942-1943, Yale University Yntema, Theodore O. (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Y, general, 1943-1944, Yale University Library Yntema, Theodore O. Young, Blanche Young, James (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Y, general, 1944-1945, Yen, Y. C. James Young, Blanche Young, Harold (Box 59, Folder 28)
- You, Dick Himmel, Daisy Chain story, 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Z, general, 1937-1938 (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Z, general, 1939-1940, Zenith Zook, George F. (Box 59, Folder 31)
- Z, general, 1940-1941, Zemurray, Samuel (Box 59, Folder 32)
- Z, general, 1941-1942, Zemurray, Samuel Zook, George F. (Box 59, Folder 33)
- Z, general, 1942-1943, Ziegler, Jerry Zimmermann, Herbert P. (Box 59, Folder 34)
- Z, general, 1943-1944, Ziebarth, E. W. Zimmermann, Herbert P. (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Z, general, 1944-1945, Ziebarth, E. W. Zimmermann, Herbert P. (Box 59, Folder 36)
- Zimmermann, Herbert P., 1937-1938 (Box 59, Folder 37)
- Zimmermann, Herbert P., 1938-1939 (Box 59, Folder 38)
- Zimmermann, Herbert P., 1939-1940 (Box 59, Folder 39)
- Zimmermann, Herbert P., 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 40)
- Zimmermann, Herbert P., 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 41)